masala.com 2019-12-02

# Privacy policy | ITP Media Group

## 1\. OUR APPROACH

1.1 This website **** and related services (collectively, the “ **Site** ”) is operated by ITP Media Group FZ-LLC (“ **ITP** ”, “ **us** ”, “ **we** ” or “ **our** ”). Our company is registered in Dubai with licence number 30006 and our registered office is at Building 14, Dubai Media City, Dubai, U.A.E

1.2 This Privacy Policy applies to the personal information we collect through our Site and how we may use it. Some of this information will enable us to identify you and is known as personal data (whether sensitive personal data or otherwise) (“ **Personal Data** ”). As required by law, we will take particular care when dealing with your Personal Data. This is part our commitment to protecting and respecting your privacy.

1.3 The terms “ **you** ”, “ **your** ”, “ **yours** ” and “ **user(s)** ” when used in this Privacy Policy refers to any visitor to or user of this Site.

1.4 Any Personal Data you supply to us via the Site (and by other means) will be treated in accordance with applicable law. Where you provide us with personal information relating to others via the Site, you confirm that you have their consent or are otherwise entitled to provide this information to us and for us to use it in the ways described in this Privacy Policy.

1.5 By proceeding with access to the Site you are deemed to have accepted the Terms and Conditions **https://www.itp.com/terms** (including the terms of this Privacy Policy). Please read them carefully as they affect your rights and liabilities under the law. If you do not agree with the Terms and Conditions as they apply to the Site, then please refrain from accessing or using the Site.          

1.6 If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact our Data Protection Compliance Manager at [legal@itp.com](mailto:legal@itp.com)

## 2\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

2.1 We reserve the right, from time to time, with or without notice to you, to change our Privacy Policy at our sole discretion. Our Privacy Policy is applicable to your access to and use of the Site will be the version that is current and accessible at each date you access the Site. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). Your use of the Site after changes are made means that you agree to be bound by such changes. If you do not wish to accept the new Privacy Policy you should not continue to use the Site.

## 3\. what information do we collect?

We may collect and store the following information:

3.1  ** _Information you give us._**

We may require you to register to use our Site. When you do, we’ll ask for [personal information](https://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy/key-terms/#toc-terms-personal-info), like your name, age, contact details, sports and lifestyle choices or [credit card](https://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy/example/credit-card.html) details to store with your account.

If you sign up to receive breaking industry news from us, we’ll ask for your name, surname, company name and email address.

From time to time we may invite users to provide information via surveys or competitions. We may collect information such as your name, contact details, post code or job title. Our Site may also have features where users can submit information to us.

3.2  ** _Information we get from your use of our Site._**

We [collect information](https://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy/example/collect-information.html) about the services that you use and how you use them, like when you view particular content on our Site or [view and interact with our ads](https://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy/example/view-and-interact-with-our-ads.html) and content.

3.3  ** _Information we generate from our Site._**

We [store information](https://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy/example/collect-information.html) that we generate from our analysis of the data you and other users of our Site have provided and in connection with your use of our Site, such as products you have bought or services you have subscribed for.

## 4\. PURPOSES FOR WHICH we process PERSONAL data

4.1 We will only process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

4.1.1 **creating and maintaining your user account** , if you become our registered user; ****

4.1.2 **offering our content, goods or providing our services to you in a personalised way** , for example, we may provide suggestions based on your previous searches to enable you to identify suitable content quicker. This may also include, where legally permitted, processing data related to your location;

4.1.3 **handling and fulfilling your orders, requests for good or services or entry into competitions**. This may also include processing of information that we receive from third parties, for example, address data to verify your correct address;

4.1.4 **obtaining payment from you** , if you purchase any of our digital content, goods and/or services;

4.1.5 **enabling our suppliers and service providers to carry out certain functions on our behalf, including payment processing, verification, technical, logistical or other functions** , as may be required, in order to fulfil your orders;

4.1.6 **resolving any returns, refunds or disputes** , if you lawfully exercise your rights or if you wish to dispute any part of our offering;

4.1.7 **ensuring the security of your account and our business, preventing or detecting fraud or abuses of our Site** , for example, by requesting verification information in order to reset your account password;

4.1.8 **developing and improving our products and services** , for example, by reviewing visits to our Site and its various subpages, demand for specific content, goods and services and user comments;

4.1.9 **sending you personalised marketing communications** , where you have agreed that we may do so, in order to keep you informed of our and our selected partner’s products and services, which we consider may be of interest to you;

4.1.10 **serving personalised advertising to your devices** ; delivering ads based on your interests ascertained from your past searches, visits of subpages and purchases on our Sites, and other data obtained through the use of "cookies" placed on your devices. Please see our Cookies statement below; and

4.1.11 **to comply with applicable law** , for example, in response to a request from a court or regulatory body, where such request is made in accordance with the law.

## 5\. Security

We are committed to ensuring that your Personal Data is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Although we endeavour to protect your Personal Data, because of the nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Site and any inward transmission of data is carried out at your own risk.

## 6\. DISCLOSURE OF USER INFORMATION

6.1 There are circumstances where we wish to disclose or are compelled to disclose your Personal Data to third parties. This will only take place in accordance with the applicable law and for the purposes listed above. These scenarios include disclosure:

6.1.1 to our subsidiaries, branches or associated offices;

6.1.2 to our outsourced service providers or suppliers to facilitate the provision of our services or goods to our Users, for example, the disclosure to our data centre provider for the safe keeping of your Personal Data, webhosting provider through which your Personal Data may be collected, identity verification partners in order to verify your identity against public databases;

6.1.3 to third party service providers and consultants in order to protect the security or integrity of our business, including our databases and systems and for business continuity reasons;

6.1.4 to another legal entity, on a temporary or permanent basis, for the purposes of a joint venture, collaboration, financing, sale, merger, reorganisation, change of legal form, dissolution or similar event. In the case of a merger or sale, your Personal Data will be permanently transferred to a successor company;

6.1.5 to our advertising partners who enable us to deliver personalised ads to your devices or similar advertising;

6.1.6 subject to your consent, to our marketing partners, who may contact you by post, email, telephone, SMS or by other means;

6.1.7 to public authorities where we are required by law to do so; and

6.1.8 to any other third party where you have provided your consent.

## 7\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA

We may transfer your Personal Data to a third party in countries outside the country in which it was originally collected for further processing in accordance with the purposes set out in paragraph above. In particular, your Personal Data may be transferred throughout the ITP Media Group and to our outsourced service providers located abroad. In these circumstances we will, as required by applicable law, ensure that your privacy rights are adequately protected by appropriate technical, organisation, contractual or other lawful means.  

## 8\. cookies

The Site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our Site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Site and also allows us to improve our Site.  By using this Site, navigating around it and using our services, you agree to the use of cookies.

## 9\. Children

Please note that this Site is not intended for children under the age of 21.

## 10\. LINKED WEBSITES

Please note that any websites that may be linked to our Sites are subject to their own privacy policy.

## 11\. Contacting us

We have endeavoured to make our terms and conditions and Privacy Policy as straightforward as possible.  However legal terms can be complicated.  If you want to get in touch regarding our services or have a general question, please contact us at: [legal@itp.com](mailto:legal@itp.com).

Last updated on 19 August 2018.

ITP Media Group  
PO Box 500024, Dubai, United Arab Emirates  
Tel.: [+971 4 444 3000](tel:0097144443000)
